tweepbee.com 2013-07-17

# Expand Your Twitter Network While Protecting Your Privacy | Tweepbee

**Tweepbee's Privacy Policy**

Tweepbee is very concerned about your privacy and strives to protect it with the highest degree of care and consideration. We also want to disclose all relevant privacy information to you for your review below.

> **1\. Definitions**

> **_Tweepbee_** \- refers specifically to the Tweepbee.com website. May also be referred to as "site" or "website."

> **_User_** \- anyone using the Tweepbee.com website.

> **_Personal Information_** __ \- any personal data or information such as name, address, phone number, email, birth date, etc.

> **_Other Data_** \- any other information not of a personal nature, which may include tweets, category selections, etc.

> **_Cookie_** \- a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from the Tweepbee web server to be stored for a specified period of time on your computer's hard drive. Tweepbee cookies do not damage, impair, change, or negatively influence your computer's activity.

> **_IP Address_** \- an Internet Protocol (IP) address that is identified by a designated number that is automatically assigned to a computer when it logs onto an internet service provider, local area network, or wide area network.

**2\. Coverage**

This privacy policy applies only to Tweepbee.com and is no longer in effect when you leave this website whether directly or via links on our site. Other websites you may visit will have their own policies and procedures.

**3\. Collection of Personal Information**

We may collect and store personal information from you during registration or while performing other activities on our website. You are never under any obligation to provide this information unless you want to utilize our services. We do not collect this information from you in any manner except through your volunteer disclosure of this information either directly from you or by using our authentication process with Twitter.com.

**4\. Collection of Other Data**

We may collect and store a variety of other information such as posts, selected categories, etc.

**5\. Use of Personal Information and Data**

Tweepbee may use your personal information and/or data when contacting you in communications related to account management, service updates, new promotions, or relevant products and services.

**6\. Sharing Your Personal Information and Data**

Tweepbee does not share your personal information or data with other companies, websites, or individuals. An exception to this is the authentication process by which you log into your Twitter account from our website and information is exchanged between our website and the Twitter website.

In addition, we may provide your personal information to government agencies when required to do so by law or in any case where we have made a decision to take legal action against you.

**7\. Use of Cookies**

Like most websites on the Internet that have login functions, we use cookies to help us provide you with the services offered by our website. This enables us to keep you logged in and display your account information and other data as necessary.

**8\. Use of IP Addresses**

In order to improve system administration and detect fraudulent activity on our website, we collect IP addresses from users. This information may be used to identify the user and to determine if user is abiding by our terms and conditions.

**9\. Information Security**

Tweepbee has taken preventive measures to implement various security protocols and procedures to protect user information and other sensitive data on our website. Only authorized employees or contractors have access to your information and only as relevant to the performance of their responsibilities.

**10\. Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy at any time by simply posting updated or changed content on this Web page and it is the user's responsibility to check this page to stay informed of our current privacy policy.

**11\. Contacting Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us at [support@tweepbee.com](http://support@tweepbee.com/).
